试想想不再有罪案…
Imagine an end to crime...
不再有贫穷
...an end to poverty.
试想有两百万份 令人满意的工作等着你去做
Imagine 2 million good jobs waiting to be filled.
听来像做梦吧？
Sounds like a dream, doesn't it?
有时候梦境会成真
Well, sometimes dreams come true.
三角洲城
Delta City.
为了我们的孩子
For our children.
这是新闻追击，给我们三分钟 我们就给你全世界
This is Media Break. You give us three minutes, we'll give you the world.
晚安，我是凯西黄 今晚的主要新闻有…
Good evening, I'm Casey Wong. Our top story tonight:
数月来的猜测告终 汽车之城变得日本化了
Motor City goes Japanese as the Omni Consumer Products Corporation...
今天普及消费者产品公司宣布…
...ended months of speculation today by announcing its takeover...
该公司会被跨国的金光公司收购
...by the multinational Kanemitsu Corporation.
乖，你快点把微积分做完 要睡觉了
Come on, honey, hurry up with your calculus. It's almost time for bed.
我在看新闻追击
I'm watching Media Break.
是第一间私有公司完全拥有和管理 一个大城市的私人机构
the first private corporation to completely own and operate a major city.
发言人表示对市区...
Company spokesmen express special interest...
重新安置问题 有特别兴趣
in the issues of urban resettlement...
还有底特律的罪案猖獗 市民都叫这做战区
...and a crime wave in Detroit that many citizens are calling a war zone.
但OCP通常都有解决办法
But as usual, OCP has an answer.
这些是建改警队 市区重建改造警察
Meet the Rehabs, Urban rehabilitation officers.
从炮火连天的亚马逊战场来的
From the blazing fields of the Amazon War...
新型市区维持治安警队
...comes state-of-the-art urban pacification.
我们是来协助市民 增强警方和对付黑道份子
We're here to help the people, augment the police force and deal with the gang problem.
有报导说 你们其实是来驱逐居民…
What about reports you're actually evicting people...
以便兴建三角洲城的
...to make way for construction of Delta City?
妮歌，听妈妈的话，来吧
Nikko, you heard your mom. Go on.
哎
Oh, man.
- 无家可归的人又怎样？ - 真滑头
- And the homeless? - What a gyp.
要拆毁一些建筑物 才能兴建三角洲城
Some buildings have to come down before Delta can go up.
我不否认我们发了 一、两张驱逐令…
I won't deny we're serving an eviction notice or two...
但大部分人都接受过 验尿和入职考试
...but most of these people have already taken their urine tests and placement exams.
有新工作等着他们做的
They've got new jobs waiting for them.
我们只是在过渡时期协助他们
We're just helping them make the transition, that's all.
- 我们是警察，别无其他 - 别无其他？
- We're cops, nothing more. - Nothing more?
我的意思是，我们不是机械人
Well, we're not robots, if that's what you mean.
爸爸？
Hey, Dad?
你该睡了
You're supposed to be asleep.
电视说的是不是真的？
Is it true what the Tv said?
外面是不是有个战区？
That it's a war zone outside?
别听电视说的 这里是你的家，知道吗？
Don't listen to what the Tv says. This is your home, you hear me?
你在这里很安全
And you're safe here.
付多少钱我也愿意！
I'll buy that for a dollar!
快走…
Get out, get out, get out!
（驱逐令）
这一区是普及消费者 产品公司的资产
This neighborhood is the property of omni Consumer Products.
（底特律卡迪拉克区）
- 天，帮帮我们 - 我们正是来帮你们
- For God's sake, help us! - That's what we're here for, ma'am.
上车
Just get on the bus.
爸爸，他们带我们去哪里？ 发生什么事？
Where are they taking us, Dad? What's happening?
别相信他们！ 他们会丢我们到街上，自生自灭
Don't believe them! They'll throw us into the streets to die like rats!
纳粹党混蛋！
Nazi sons of bitches!
有需要时就射死她，但把她带走
Shoot her if you must, but get her out of here.
知道
Yes, sir.
走吧
Let's go. Come on.
我认为进展得不错，是不是？
I think it's going rather well, don't you?
是的
Yes, sir.
我叫你快点，走吧
Come on, I said, move! Move!
- 你对老妇粗暴点，好吗？ - 闭嘴！
- Manandle an old lady, would you? - Shut up!
- 走！ - 上车
- Move, move! - Get up there!
我叫你起来！
I said, get up!
你在下面干嘛？笨蛋
What are you doing down there? Piece of slime!
听到我说吗？
Can you hear me?
我叫你起来，笨蛋！
I said, get up, you drunken cow!
退后！那架起重机会爆炸！
Get back! The crane's gonna blow!
大家听着，这些巴士 那儿也去不了
Listen to me, people! These buses are going nowhere!
留下来，为你们的家园抗争 根本不会有好日子
Stay here! Fight for your homes! There is no silver lining!
只是那些机构混蛋想中饱私囊
Only corporate scumbags who want to line their pockets!
妮歌！…
Nikko! Nikko!
妈妈！爸爸！
Mom! Mom! Dad!
妮歌！不！那是我的孩子，妮歌
Nikko! No! That's my baby! Nikko, Nikko!
妈妈！爸爸！
Mom! Dad! Dad!
Mom, Dad!
妈妈！
Mom!
爸爸！
Dad?!
妈妈！
Mom!
你！别走开！
You! Stay where you are!
重复，建改警队是来协助你们的
Repeat: The rehabilitation officers are here to assist you.
没事的，你现在跟我们一起
It's okay, it's okay. You're with us now.
他走了没有？
Is he gone?
我们是否安全？
Are we clear?
安全
Clear!
好，我们来吧
Okay, let's do it.
好了，莫连奴
Okay, Moreno.
掩着耳朵
Cover your ears.
来吧
Rock 'r roll.
没有人，我们走吧
All clear. Let's go.
天
Jesus!
- ED209 - 他不在侦察照片里
- ED 209! - He wasrt in the recon photo!
别动！你们擅自闯进警方范围
Freeze! You are trespassing on police property.
放下武器
Please surrender your weapons.
- 什么事？ - 她疯的吗？
- What the hell? - Is she crazy?
你们有二十秒时间
You have 20 seconds to comply.
- 孩子，回来 - 你会害死我们的！
- Hey, kid, come back here! - You're gonna get us all killed!
她到底在干什么？
What the hell is she doing?
你们直接违反了 法例第114条，第3节
You are in direct violation of penal code 114, section 3.
我有权使用武力
I am authorized to use physical force.
你们现在有十秒时间
You now have 10 seconds to comply.
你们不会相信的 他会像头小狗般忠心
You won't believe this. He'll be loyal as a puppy.
你们有五秒、四秒…
You have five seconds. Four seconds.
三秒，你们有一秒时间
Three seconds. You have one second to comply.
我现在有权…
I am now authorized to...
像头小狗般忠心
...be loyal as a puppy.
厉害！
Damn!
会有效吗？
Will it work?
从一个死了的警察偷来的
Stole it off a dead cop.
（有人闯入）
该死，是警方军火库
Holy shit! That's the police armory!
- 他们取消了通行识认 - 我们快走！
- They deleted the access signature. - Let's get out of here!
我们几分钟后才到达 我们想办法打开这扇门
They'll be a few minutes. Let's figure out how to open that door!
你开玩笑吧？
Are you kidding me?
一站式购物呢
One-stop shopping.
- 快走！要立刻离开！ - 走
- Let's go! Gotta get out of here! - He's right. Let's ride.
- 你干嘛？选窗帘布？ - 来了
- What are you, picking out drapes? - Coming!
- 拿那个 - 为什么？
- Get that. - Why?
它看来很昂贵
It looks expensive.
我们走吧！
Come on! Come on, let's go!
放下武器！
Drop your weapons now!
快点，放下武器！
Do it! Drop them!
别动！你们擅自闯进警方范围
Freeze! You're trespassing on police property.
混蛋，去死吧！
Eat lead, suckers!
妮歌，快上车！
Nikko, get in! Come on!
有什么可效劳？
What can I do for you?
别动！
Nobody move!
把收银机里的钱拿来，快点
Everything in the register! Now! Do it!
当火箭科学家是什么滋味？
What's it like being a rocket scientist?
所有单位注意，警方范围里 发生破门闯入事件，请回应
All units, we have a B and E involving police property, please respond.
重复，所有单位注意…
Repeat, all units, we have a...
唐诺利，轮到你了
Hey, Donnelly, it's your turn.
- 不行，我们上次去了 - 不，轮到路易斯
- No way. We went last time. - No, it's Lewis' turn.
路易斯，到你去
Lewis, you're up.
路易斯…
Lewis! Lewis! Lewis!
究竟有没有人要拘捕我？
Isn't anybody gonna arrest me, or what?!
- 你朋友摩菲去了哪里？ - 他不喜欢吃甜甜圈的
- Where's your friend Murphy? - He's not big on doughnuts.
- 他不喜欢吃甜甜圈 - 我知道
- He's not big on doughnuts. - I knew that.
所有单位注意，重复 是一辆残旧的黄色小型货车
All units, repeat, that is a battered yellow van.
没有牌照 追踪器显示朝南面走
No plates. Tracking shows southbound...
- 那是辆残旧的黄色小型货车 - 不错
- That's a battered yellow van. - No shit, Sherlock.
莫连奴，我们有伴了
Moreno, company's coming!
抓稳点，来吧
Hold on. Here we go.
单位477正在追踪 朝东面艾普西道走
Unit 477 in pursuit, eastbound, Esposito.
小心！
Watch it!
我很小心
I'm watching it!
天
Jesus!
他们还追着我们
They're still on our tail.
不用怕
Don't sweat it.
孩子，看这个
Hey, kid. Watch this.
别高兴得太早
Hold the champagne.
你停在马路中心
You stopped in the middle of the street!
- 我是绿灯 - 笨蛋！
- That was my light! - You idiot!
- 大家没事吧？ - 没事？你说笑吗？
- Is everybody okay? - Okay? What are you, a comedian?
我用一辆全新SUX换的，看看
I traded in a brand new SUX for this classic. Now look at it!
真是垃圾，去废车场好了
It's garbage. It's going to the junkyard.
这是什么？给婆娘一个徽章 她就以为自己是老板
What is this, fellas? You give a broad a badge and she gets delusions of gander.
是权势，笨蛋
It's "grandeur," dumbshit.
这个新人令我紧张
This new guy is making me nervous.
我相信这不是人类
I don't think this is exactly a guy.
是不是他？
You think it's him?
单位477叫调遣部
Unit 477 to dispatch.
477叫调遣部，请通话
This is 477 to dispatch. Come in, dispatch.
我们需要支援
We could use some backup out here.
调遣部，请通话，这是477
Hello, dispatch. Come in. This is 477 to dispatch.
路易斯
Lewis.
霹雳党
Splatterpunks.
等一下，你们拿着机关枪干嘛？
Wait a second, what do you need the shotgun for?
我们都要死了
Shit, we're all gonna die.
- 别动，支援快到了 - 别动？
- Sit tight, people. Backup's coming. - Sit tight?
要不是你，我也不会在这里 笨婆娘
If it wasrt for you, I wouldn't even be here, you dumb broad.
我跟你作个协议 你想吃掉领带就继续闹吧
I'll make you a deal, tough guy. You want to eat the tie, keep it up.
放松点，我哥哥是个警察
Take it easy. My brother's a cop.
477叫调遣部，紧急事故 我们子弹不足，需要支援
477 to dispatch, code 3! We're low on ammo and need immediate backup!
马上来
Right now!
瑞德警官
Sergeant Reed.
我在位置图上看到摩菲的巡逻车
I got Murphy's cruiser on the grid.
- 他刚调头了 - 什么？
- He just turned around. - He what?!
摩菲，我是瑞德
Murphy, this is Reed.
我派了三辆车去声援路易斯
I have three other vehicles en route to Lewis.
摩菲，继续追踪 这是个直接命令，明白吗？
Murphy, continue pursuit! That is a direct order! Do I make myself clear?
摩菲，你是否听…
Murphy, are you listen...?
警察，不准游荡
Police officer. No loitering.
你需要支援？
You called for backup?
谢谢你来，摩菲
Thanks for dropping by, Murphy.
他们走了没有？
Are they gone?
我扫描到还有三个人
I'm still scanning three.
剩下两个人
Make that two.
快躲避，大攻击来了
Block it! Megazone invasion!
冷静点，笨蛋，霹雳围是我们的
Pop a tranq, hypo-head. Splatterville's ours.
射他的嘴
Shoot him in the mouth.
半机械人要吃子弹了
Cyborg eats bullets, Jock.
今晚他不吃
Not tonight he don't.
射他的嘴
Hit him in the mouth!
- 闭嘴 - 做吧
- Shut up! - Do it! Do it!
- 做吧 - 闭嘴
- Do it! Do it! - Shut up!
试得好，变态鬼
Nice try, creeps.
给我！
Give me it!
你们有权保持缄默
You have the right to remain silent.
在那边
Down there.
天，摩菲，你没事吧？
Jesus, Murphy, are you okay?
我很好，安妮
I'm fine, Anne.
谢谢关心
Thank you for asking.
快点…
Come on, come on!
快走，不会有事的
Let's go! Everything will be all right.
放手
Get your damn hands off me!
笨孩子
Stupid kid.
（录影中）
- 过来 - 你别管那个孩子好吗？
- Come here. Come on. - Would you forget the stupid kid already?!
（录影中）
无能的美国人
你们又肥又懒惰
现在不单是钱财上受到威胁
你越犯大错…
我们的竞争对手就越笑得大声
你们的行动令我们双方蒙羞
金光先生
Kanemitsu-san...
我知道我们遭受挫折
...I realize we've had setbacks...
但我们已经尽一切努力 让三角洲城如期复工
...but we've done everything possible to get Delta City back on schedule.
你们的能力都表露无遗了
我会派一个特工来 修正你们的错误
各位…
Gentlemen...
本公司正面临…
...you are now looking at a company...
过渡时期
...in transition.
不用说 这样做已导致执行上某些…
Needless to say, this has resulted in the implementation of certain...
嗯
...well...
我们称它们为…
...let's call them...
削减
..."cutbacks."
但谁能为梦想估价？
But who can put a price tag on a dream?
我们受人敬重的前主席 有一个梦想
Our esteemed former chairman had a dream.
他叫它做三角洲城
He called it Delta City.
别这样，强生
Knock it off, Johnson.
各位，伟大的底特律市 代表着一个重要的先河
The great city of Detroit represents an important precedent, gentlemen.
但有一个小问题
There's only one small problem.
它变成了一个战区
It's turning into a war zone!
是个小规模反抗组织巴了
It's just a small resistance group.
他们不会构成重大威胁
There's no reason to believe they pose a significant threat.
我认为…
I'd consider...
三亿五千万元的赤字 是个重大威胁
...a deficit of 350 million dollars a significant threat.
是不是？
Wouldrt you?
- 费历克 - 先生
- Fleck! - Sir.
你主管保安概念部
You're in charge of Security Concepts.
我们耗资巨大的机械警察在哪里？
Where's that Robocop we spent so much money on?
警方对那个装置有问题 我正在处理
The police had a problem with the unit. I'm dealing with it personally.
你快做
You do that.
派他去建改组
Get him to the Rehab Team...
我们也许就不用担心 一个小规模反抗组织了
...and maybe we won't have to worry about a "small resistance group."
你们快滚出去
Get the hell out of here, all of you!
你们慢慢来
You take your time.
天，费历克…
And for God's sake, Fleck...
尝试拉拢警方帮我们
...try to get the police on our side.
若我不想有个机械人在我队中呢？
What if I don't want a robot on my team?
保罗麦代格，你有四天时间
You've got 4 days, McDaggett.
若卡迪拉克区在周五凌晨 还未清场进行拆毁…
If Cadillac Heights isn't cleared for demolition Friday midnight...
我们会被追讨贷款 OCP就会完蛋
...our loans will be called in. OCP will be ruined.
我们有个协议的，是吗？
We made a deal, didn't we, chum.
顺便一提…
Oh, by the way...
如果你觉得做大生意 和作战的界线…
...if you're just figuring out the line between big business and war...
有点模糊不清…
...is a little blurry...
那么你就是 比他们口中说得好要糟
...then you're further over the hill than they say.
（金光世界总部）
但是，金光先生
我们从没派过雄志 去这么人口稠密的地区
不要再讨论了
（西区警察局）
这是诱捕，我的当事人当时 在那间旅馆探访朋友
This is entrapment! My client was visiting close friends in that motel.
你当事人的朋友们…
Hey, buddy. Your client's friends...
是一支非工会摄影组 和一头德国牧羊狗
...were a non-union video crew and a German shepherd.
那有偏见
That's prejudicial.
那个负责拘捕的警员 有否要求看他们的工会证？
Did the arresting officer ask to see their union cards?
来处理这个，听电话好吗？
Come get this crap. Will someone answer the damn phone?!
西区，不，小姐，我们没有巴工
Metro West. No, ma'am, we're not on strike.
你本可以骗倒我 我会处置那班劫匪
You could have fooled me. I'll deal with those looters myself.
给我一支有钉的垒球棒
Get me a baseball bat with some nails in it.
你觉得怎样？
How are you feeling?
不大好
I've been better.
老实说，你像跟一辆货车做了朋友
To be honest, it looks like you just made friends with a Mack truck.
我没有很多…
I don't have many...
朋友
...friends.
赖莎拉斯博士
Dr. Lazarus.
- 发生了什么事？ - 阿特兰大队昨晚打赢活塞队
- You want to tell me what happened? - Atlanta beat the Pistons last night.
- 很有趣，我是指英勇小子 - 是他
- That's cute. I meant with glory boy. - Oh, him.
他受到枪击，还着了火
He got shot to hell and set on fire.
你明白我的意思 他违抗直接命令，为什么？
You know what I'm talking about. He disobeyed a direct order. Why?
- 我真正的意见？ - 不，说谎，编个故事
- My real opinion? - No, lie. Make up a story.
费历克先生…
Well, Mr. Fleck...
目前…
...offhand...
我认为他抗命的唯一理由是…
...l'd say the only reason he'd disobey an order is if...
他不同意那个命令
...he didn't agree with it.
什么？
Excuse me?
他作了一个决定
He made a decision.
他的朋友有麻烦 他作出判断，警察都那样做的
His friend was in trouble, he made a judgment call. Cops do that.
人类的警察，你说“他的朋友” 是什么意思？它是副机器
Human cops. What do you mean, "his friend"? It's a machine.
听着
Look,
如果OCP只要一个机械人 为何他们派摩菲去那里？
if oCP just wanted a robot, why'd they put Murphy in there in the first place?
摩菲已经死了，已有记录在案
Murphy's dead, sweetheart, that's on record.
费历克先生，这就是摩菲
Mr. Fleck, this is Murphy!
在他的面孔,大脑,小脑所留下的..
What's left of his face, his cerebrum, his cerebellum.
人体组织仍然存在
Human tissue that's still alive.
为何结合两者...
How can you interface human and machine...
但当人类部分作决定时又要抱怨？
then complain when the human part makes a decision?
那么我们不单得到了 摩菲多年来的训练…
So not only did we get Murphy's years of training...
和执法技巧，还继承了…
and his law-enforcement skills, we also inerited...
他的记忆、感觉和情绪？
...his memories, his feelings, his emotional baggage?
我会叫它做他的人性 但我相信你不认识那个字眼
Well, I'd call it his humanity, but I don't think you know that word.
是吧
I see.
你说服我了，删除他的情感
You talked me into it. His emotions: Get rid of them.
找出它们的位置后消除它们 如果洗掉他的记忆，那真糟糕
Find their location and erase them. If it wipes out his memory, too bad.
我们可以植入一个 微型神经障碍器…
We could cut out the appropriate circuits by...
截断有关的线路
...implanting a micro-neuro-barrier.
做吧
Do it.
听着，我不管你有多聪明
I got news for you. I don't give a shit how smart you are.
OCP拥有警队 拥有他、还拥有你
OCP owns the cops. That means they own him, and they own your cute little ass.
没有人能拥有我
Nobody owns me.
很好
Fine.
我们要他加入建改队
We want him on the Rehab Team.
你把他改为可以预测 否则你另谋高就
That means you make him predictable, or look for a new job, sweet cheeks.
我堕入爱河了
I think I'm in love.
你脑海中想着什么？
What's going through your head?
（记忆搜寻：摩菲）
那是他的家人
That's his family.
可要我安装那个神经障碍器？
Want me to install the neuro-barrier, doctor?
不，我可以做
No, I can do it.
我想单独陪着他
I think I'd like to be alone with him, if it's all right.
（记忆搜寻：）
摩菲，我以为你永远不回来了
Alex, I thought you'd never get home.
别让那些无家可归的人动摇你们
Don't let the fact that these people are homeless sway you.
他们都是恐怖分子
They're terrorists, pure and simple.
画面上的都是可疑的叛军位置
On the screens are suspected rebel locations.
若这些地点在你们的巡逻范围内 便去查看一下
If these locations appear on your regular beat, check it out.
报告任何不寻常的发现…
Make sure you report any unusual findings...
有听到他们怎样处置摩菲吗？
Hear what they did to Murphy?
（重播）
摩菲
Murphy.
路易斯，要不要盔甲？
Lewis, you want your body armor?
什么？ 不要，我下班了
What? No, I'm off duty.
到底什么事？
What's up, anyway?
你有没有家人？
Do you have family?
有，有个在匹兹堡从不打电话 给我的弟弟，你知道的
Yeah, I have a brother in Pittsburgh, the one who never calls. You know that.
机械人，你没事吧？
Robo, are you okay?
我很好
I'm fine.
叫我摩菲
And call me Murphy.
（热能图像）
摩菲？
Murphy?
离开这座建筑物
Step out of the building.
留在原地
Stay right there.
我们是警察
We're police officers.
我们不需要你们
We don't want you.
里面有一些擅闯者 别靠近那扇门
We believe there are squatters in there. Now step away from the door.
他们是平民，他们想取暖巴了
They're civilians. They're just trying to stay warm!
这些人是属于一所改造中心的
Those people belong in the nearest rehabilitation center.
（首要指令一：为公众服务）
部分是恐怖分子 走开，否则你会被控阻碍办公
Some are terrorists. Step away or you will be cited for obstructing justice.
（二：保护无辜者）
我不会再礼貌地要求了
I'm not going to ask politely next time.
别靠近那扇门
Step away from the door.
（三：执行法纪）
这是你们的最后警告
This is your final warning.
（四：不准违抗OCP人员）
你们犯了个错误
You are making a mistake.
- 退后，否则会有麻烦 - 这样才对
- Back off, or there'll be trouble. - Now you're talking, Murphy.
我们不会让步 你们开枪射我们吧
We're not budging. If you wanna get in, you'll have to shoot through us.
我不觉得那有大问题
I don't have a huge problem with that.
（瞄准中 四：不准违抗OCP人员）
停火
Cease fire!
（系统损毁警报，效率72%）
机械警察
Robocop.
（效率69%）
快 快 快
Come on, come on, come on!
跟我们走吧
Come with us!
掩护我
Cover me.
我是个精锐的警察 是不是，伙伴？
Some tough cop I am. Huh, partner?
我很害怕
I'm scared.
不要怕
Don't be.
不会痛太久的
It won't hurt long.
（记录）
替我抓他们
Get them for me.
答应我
Promise me.
我答应你
I promise.
摩菲
Murphy.
警员身亡
Officer down.
快走
Move it!
没时间了
We don't have much time.
妮歌，我们走吧
Nikko, let's go.
快点，跟我们走
Come on. Come with us.
他是个警察，是他们的人
Is she crazy? He's a cop! He's one of them!
他现在是我们的人
He's on our side now.
她说得对，你看到他做的事
She's right. You saw what he did.
你让个笨小孩替我们作决定？
You'll let a stupid kid make our decisions?
- 我们去作战，我们需要他帮忙 - 你说笑吗？看他
- We're at war. We can use his help. - Are you kidding me? Look at him!
他毁烂不堪
He is totaled, man!
来吧，没时间争论了
People, come on. We don't have time for this shit.
他说得对
He's right.
我们该走了
We should go.
在五米范围内周围搜索
Five-meter spread. Search the perimeter.
该死
Damn.
- 长官，他在移动 - 不可能的，整个建筑物都被包围了
- We're tracking him, sir. He's moving. - Impossible. The building is surrounded.
他走到地下去了
He's gone underground.
找个入口
Find a manole.
我们有点阻碍
We got a little held up.
老鼠？
Rats?
一两只吧
One or two.
（热能图像）
走过去
Go on through.
（系统损毁警报，效率25%）
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我很好
I'm fine.
你
Hey!
你们快来
You guys!
天
Oh, man!
我叫你不要带他来的
I told you it was a mistake to bring him.
他重得要命
I bet he weighs a ton.
小心
Watch your step.
好吧
All right.
让开
Clear the way.
- 让开 - 扶着你那一边
- Get out of the way. - Hold up your side.
他看来不妙
He don't look good.
你胸口中了手榴弹也会不妙
You wouldn't look so good either if you took a grenade in your chest.
追踪
Tracking.
- 信标 - 追踪？
- Beacon. - Tracking?
他会带领他们找到来的
He'll lead them right to us!
闭嘴，康斯
Shut up, Coontz!
他在说什么？
What's he talking about?
- 他可有在入口设下陷阱？ - 可能吧
- Did he booby-trap the 8th Street entrance? - Maybe.
我们还是快走
Better get mobilized, folks.
那次他们几乎得手
They got a little too close to home that time.
这是不值得的
It's not won'th it.
根本不值得
It's not won'th this shit!
你最好深深吸一口气
You better take a real deep breath right now, Coontz.
因为如果你认为这样不值得…
Because if you don't think it's won'th it...
你就死定了 明白吗？
...then you're nothing but excess baggage. Do you hear me?!
你想清楚
You get it together, Coontz.
卡迪拉克区可能不算得什么 但它是我们的家
Cadillac Heights may not be much, but it's our home.
我们只有它
It's all we got.
如果你认为我们的家园不值得 告诉我什么才值得
If you don't think our homes is won'th it, then tell me what the hell is.
贝黛叫基地行动组，请通话
This is Bertha to Base op. We're coming in.
设置一个新地方
Set an extra place.
我们会带一个朋友来
We're bringing in a friend.
有来电
Incoming caller.
你想怎样？
What do you want?
美人，做得好
Nice work, dollface.
你是什么意思？
What you talking about?
你没听到吗？
You haven't heard?
不如看看新闻追击吧
You might want to turn on Media Break.
开电视，378频道
Tv on, channel 378.
目击这次悲惨开枪事件的 是建改队指挥官保罗麦代格
Witness to the tragic shooting was Rehab Commander, Paul McDaggett.
我只能说 这次损失了一个良好的公仆
All I can say is it's a terrible loss of a fine public servant.
她被自己的伙伴射死 真是难以置信
It's hard to believe that she was gunned down by her own partner.
OCP发言人证实
An OCP spokesperson has confirmed...
机械警察已经加入了叛军
that Robocop has joined the terrorist rebel forces.
他拥有大量武器，是个危险人物
He is heavily armed and should be considered extremely dangerous.
关电视
Tv off.
恭喜你，美人儿，听着 我要你…
Congratulations, sweet cheeks. Now listen up. I want your legendary ass...
带着你的工作证到我的办公室
...and your corporate I.D. Card in my office...
你不会被起诉
And maybe you won't be brought up on charges.
你考虑一下你要帮哪一边吧
Meantime, you might want to decide whose side you're on.
晚安
Sleep tight.
通话完毕 收费时间一分三秒
- 他什么？ - 向建改队开枪和做地下工作
- He what? - Shot at Rehabs and went underground.
- 我们的公关预算泡汤了 - 公司说他叛变了
- There goes our P.R. Budget. - Company line is he's gone renegade.
- 总管有何反应？ - 你认为会怎样？
- How'd the CEo take it? - How do you think?
我跟你说，总管很生气
Between me and you, I think the CEo's losing it.
看看周围
I mean, take a look around, will you?
这里像罗马帝国倒台一样
It's the Fall of Rome around here.
岌岌可危，你明白吗？
It's Darwin time, you know what I'm saying?
有用的才能生存
Survival of the least expendable.
记得旧老板吧 所有人都可以被牺牲
Remember the old man. Everyone's expendable.
不是那么糟糕的
It can't be that bad.
亲爱的，你听到吗？
Honey, can you hear me?
你在吗？
Are you there?
每间公司都有这个情况的
Every corporation goes through this sort of thing.
天啊 发生了什么？
Oh, my God, what happened?
发生什么事？
What's happening?
阿诺跳楼了
Arnott just went out the window.
- 那是本月的第四宗 - 胆小鬼
- That's the fourth one this month. - Chickenshit.
我会选择吞枪自杀
I'd eat a bullet myself.
没那么张扬
Less showy.
我们跟那间混帐金光公司 合作的那一刻
The writing was on the wall the minute we hopped...
就已经心知肚明
...in the sack with that shitty Kanemitsu corporation.
正如我说…
As I was saying...
我们有捉拿机械警察的拘捕令
...we have a warrant out for Robocop's arrest.
如果我们把他铲除 我们认为那些擅闯者…
If we can eliminate him, then we'll find that the squatters are more...
就更容易被说服
...let's say, easily persuaded.
- 费历克 - 先生
- Fleck! - Sir.
老板，抱歉打扰你
I'm sorry for the intrusion, sir.
保安概念部有什么可以做的？
Anything Security Concepts can do?
保安概念部可以去死 你被开除了
Security Concepts can kiss my freckled butt. You're fired.
你听到吧，你被开除了，滚
You heard me! You're fired. Get out of here.
三天后就有大灾难
Three days until disaster.
我怎样向股东们解释？
What the hell will I tell my shareholders?
增加建改队人手如何？
What about more Rehabs, sir?
我们可以从警察部招募的
We could recruit them out of the Police Department.
他们比雇佣兵更便宜
It would be cheaper than mercenaries...
我们可以利用西区警察局作试点
...and we could use the Metro West facility as a staging area.
给他们象征式的加薪以作鼓励
Give them a nominal raise for an incentive.
强生，你是个好人
You're a good man, Johnson.
我知道我提升你做副总裁 是有原因的
I knew there was a reason I made you a vice president.
过奖，老板
Thank you, sir.
我真的…
I really...
（暴虐的资本主义蠢猪）
接着
Heads up!
快点，我们要迟到了
Come on, let's go. We're gonna be late!
怎样？
Well?
你能否修理他？
Can you fix him?
这不是修理汽车活门
This isn't a valve job on a Chevy.
我从没修理过机械警察
I never worked on a damn Robocop before.
- 我可以修理机身，但是… - 听着
- I can do the body work, but... - Look...
我们要多保卫着卡迪拉克区三天
...we gotta hang on to the Heights for three more days.
- 他能否支持到那时？ - 你有没有听我说？！
- He can hold out till then, can't he? - Are you listening to me?!
他损毁严重，我们也没有仪器
He's messed up. We don't have the equipment.
谁有？
Who the hell does?!
赖莎拉斯
Lazarus.
去找…
Find doctor...
赖莎拉斯
Lazarus.
你是谁？
Who are you?
我是机械警察的朋友
I'm friends with Robocop.
他不在这里，抱歉
Well, he's not here. I'm sorry.
你不相信我
You don't believe me.
坦白说，我不知道该相信什么
To tell you the truth, I don't know what to believe anymore.
他要我带个话给你
He had a message for you.
他说感谢你没有洗掉他的记忆
He said to thank you for not taking his memories away.
好…
Well, well, well.
恐怕你来迟一步了
Afraid you're a little late, pal.
你一定是金光的人
You must be one of Kanemitsu's boys.
我很钦佩
I'm impressed.
问题是…
Trouble is...
你的老板…
...your boss...
他拥有OCP
...he kind of owns oCP.
而OCP是我们的死对头
And oCP's kind of on our shitlist with a bullet!
你想知道叛军在哪里？
So you want to know where the rebels are?
你可以叫你的老板去死
You can tell your bosses to kiss my ass!
有一辆车正在驶近
A vehicle is approaching.
摩菲，你好吗？
How you doing, Murphy?
不大好
I've been better.
- 给我一个状态扫描 - 生物体没有受损
- Give me a status scan. - Organics intact.
系统效率23%
Systems efficiency: 23 percent.
心脏直接受撞击
Looks like a direct hit to the heart.
我们要重新调校充气系统
We have to recalibrate the pneumatic system.
他会不会死？
Is he gonna die?
我帮到它就不会的
Not if I can help it.
接到发电机吧
Let's get everything hooked up to the generator.
我们有工作要做
We've got work to do.
听这，我要暂时关掉你的能源
I'm going to unplug you for a little while.
（系统损毁警报，效率12%）
放心，不会有事的
Don't worry, everything's gonna be okay.
拿着
Here you go.
我找到你要的那个心脏
I got that heart you wanted.
我说要日产，那是金光
I said a Nissan. That's a Kanemitsu.
泽克，我们要那支密封胶，泽克
Zack, we need that sealant! Zack!
玛莉…看！
Marie! Marie! Look!
不好了
Oh, shit.
拿那块胸部金属板来
Bring me that chest plate over here.
等一会
You wait, man.
你会没事的
You are gonna be so cherry.
莫连奴，小心那个…
Moreno, watch out for the...
你干什么？
What the hell are you doing?
我不知道那东西在那里
I didn't know that thing was there!
- 别向我大叫 - 那么，不要那样做
- Don't yell at me! - Well, don't do it.
（首要指令一，为公众服务）
（二，保护无辜者 三，执行法纪）
（四，不准违抗OCP人员）
（四，已被删除）
摩菲
Murphy.
是你
It's you.
摩菲，我以为你永远不会回来了
Alex, I thought you'd never get home.
（指令记忆设定 系统状态良好）
摩菲，欢迎你
Welcome home, Murphy.
我睡不着
I couldn't sleep.
你觉得怎样？
How are you feeling?
我的效率现在是93%
My efficiency rate is 93 percent.
90以上都是正常
Anything above 90 is considered normal.
我听到玛莉叫你做摩菲
I heard Marie call you Murphy.
那是你的真名字吗？
Is that your real name?
以前是的…
It was...
之前…
...before...
之前什么？
Before what?
所以
So...
你现在复原了，你会留下来吗？
Now that you're better, will you stay?
你会不会帮我们？
Will you help us?
你知道贝黛说什么吧 若我们抵抗建改队多两天…
You know what Bertha says. If we hold back the Rehabs for two more days...
他们就不能逼我们搬迁
...they can't make us move.
他们就要释放我爸妈 我们会一家团聚
And they'll have to let my parents go. We'll all be together like family again.
你的爸妈？
Your parents?
（身亡）
摩菲？你没事吧？
Murphy? You okay?
你想念他们吗？
Your parents, you miss them?
想念
Yeah.
但是…
But...
你记着他们
...you remember them.
因为…
Because...
如果你记着他们…
...if you remember them...
他们就没有真正离开过
...they're never really gone.
摩菲…
Hey, Murphy...
我很高兴你新的心脏有效
...l'm glad your new heart works.
我听到一些声音
I heard voices.
她该上床睡了
She should be in bed.
她可以再留…
Could you leave her...
一会儿吗？
...just a moment?
当然可以
Of course.
你要付钱的
You gotta pay for that.
你聋的吗？
What are you, deaf?
混…
Son of a...
我们不是那么说的
That's not what we said.
我们不是说要那样做的
It's not what we said we were gonna do!
你说要迁移那些武器
Bertha, you said to relocate the weapons...
但这东西要放在哪里？
...but where do you want this thing?
我的天
Oh, my God.
你怎么找到这个的？
How did you get this?
从警方那里偷来的，为什么？
We stole it from the police depot. Why?
看似是F27拆下来的排气系统
This looks like the exhaust system from an F-27.
它是机械警察的飞行装置蓝本
No. It's the prototype for Robo's flight pack.
在我们测试它前，经费就耗尽了
The funding ran out before we got a chance to test it.
- 你怎么知道这么多？ - 是我设计的
- How do you know so much about it? - I designed it.
看来我们取胜的机会增大了
Well, looks like the odds on the home team just went up.
它会听从你的...
What I've done is programmed the command system...
硬体指挥
to take its cues from your hard drive.
我还把它改装成一个辅助驱进器
I've also rigged it to work as an auxiliary power unit.
如果你的动力下降…
So if you ever have a power drain like yesterday...
只要接上飞行装置再充电就行
...just interface with the flight pack and recharge whether you fly or not.
看到那些电阻器吗？
Nikko, see those resistors over there?
麻烦你给我，好吗？
Get them for me, will you?
替我抓他们
Get them for me.
答应我
Promise me.
替我抓他们
Get them for me.
答应我
Promise me.
什么事？
What's going on?
对不起
Excuse me.
你去哪里？
Hey, where you going?
做未做完的事
Unfinished business.
不要紧，他会回来的
It's okay. He'll be back.
他也需要我们
He needs us too.
他要去哪里？
Where's he going?
履行承诺
To keep a promise.
你们有个机械警察 有没有外星人警察？
You got a Robocop. You got an alien cop?
- 有没有幽灵警察？ - 我没有时间…
- Got a ghost cop? - I don't have time for...
有没有吸血殭尸警察？
You got a vampire cop?
- 摩菲 - 晚安，瑞德警官
- Murphy. - Good evening, Sergeant Reed.
你可知道有拘捕令要逮捕你？
Do you know there's a warrant out for your arrest?
知道
Yes.
我问问巴了，有什么可以效劳？
I was just checking. What can I do for you?
请指示我建改队试点的位置
Please direct me to the Rehab Staging Area.
在走廊前端，你会找到的
It's down the hall. You can't miss it.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你可能要通知消防队了
You may want to call the fire department.
- 有没有火？ - 有的
- You got a light? - Sure, man.
让我来吧，混蛋
Allow me, scum.
该死
Oh, shit.
（盘问状态）
保罗麦代格在哪里？
Where's McDaggett?
那里不像一间警察局
That does not look like a police station.
对，我不是在警察局里
You're damn right I'm not at the station.
如果不是我的探子警告我 我现在已经死了
If my spy hadrt warned me, I'd be dead now.
我以为你那个该死的忍者 会对付机械警察
I thought your damn ninja was supposed to take care of Robocop.
说好了，我清理那一区 他就不让那个机械人找我麻烦
That's the deal. I clear the area, he keeps the robot off my back.
你有没有我调派给你的装置？
You have the device I sent you?
还不用那个 也不会用，放松点
It hasn't come to that yet. And it won't. Relax.
若我不清楚你的做法
It is difficult for me to continue our business relationship...
我们很难合作下去的
...when I don't know your methods.
你不必知道我的做法
You don't need to know my methods.
我一定会清理那一区
I said I'll clear the area and I'll clear it.
你别让那个机械警察烦我就是了
Just get the robot cop off my back.
我知道你会付厚酬 去得到叛军总部的地点
I understand you're willing to pay good money to know where the rebel base is.
是的
Yes, well...
报酬很丰厚
...the money's good...
如果情报准确的话
...if the tip's good.
上次的情报救了你一命，是吧？
The last tip saved your ass, didn't it?
这里有什么？
What do we have here?
你不喜欢穿制服的男人？
You don't like men in uniform?
我爸爸刚失业 我需要一点钱巴了
My dad lost his job. I just need some money.
- 我们有钱 - 不要
- We've got lots of money, honey. - Don't.
- 不要 - 她说不要
- No! - She said, "No."
你们听觉有问题吗？
Maybe you have a hearing problem?
小姐，回家吧
Go home, young lady.
你违反了宵禁条例
You are in violation of curfew.
保罗麦代格在哪里？
Where's McDaggett?
212号房
Room 212.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我希望你买了保险
I hope you are insured.
电梯门坏的
Elevator door sticks!
不要
Don't.
路易斯警员托我带个话给你
I have a message from officer Lewis.
停车
Stop!
开车
Drive!
我叫你开车
I said, drive, goddamn it, drive!
我的时间、金钱 我不会再说了，明白吗？
My time, my money. I told you and won't tell you again, understand?
我要征用你的汽车作警方用途
I must commandeer your vehicle for police use.
你有什么问题，混蛋？
What is your problem, sucker?
我是指…长官
I mean, officer.
掩护我
Cover me.
指挥官
Commander!
（警告：儿童在玩耍）
什么事？
What's the deal?
机械警察去了哪里？
Where the hell is Robocop?
我们可以开车听一下 哪里有爆炸声
We could drive around and listen for explosions.
是你做的吗？
Are you doing that?
我厌倦了焊接电线 所以放进一个脉冲流速解码器
I got tired of splicing wires, so I put in a pulse tach decoder.
- 摇测的？ - 不是
- Telemetric? - No.
- 真聪明 - 你才聪明，我算得上什么？
- Smart ass. - I know you are, but what am I?
让我试试
Here, let me try.
谢谢你，吓我们一跳
Thanks for the heart attack.
我会派遣一支侦察队出去
I believe I will go and send out a recon team.
我有个更好的方法
I got a better idea.
不如我们都坐下来
Why don't we just all have a seat.
和放松
And relax.
几分钟内就会结束
It'll all be over in a few minutes.
你这个混蛋
You son of a bitch.
小心说话，有孩子在场
Watch the language, there's children present.
放下它，康斯
Drop it, Coontz.
我不会重复说的
I'm not going to ask twice.
你是什么意思？ 几分钟内就结束？
What do you mean, "it'll all be over in a few minutes"?
快带孩子们离开，快点
Get the kids out of here! Now!
贝黛
Bertha!
走
Go.
- 要去救她 - 快走
- Got to get her. - Go!
来吧，快走
Come on, let's go! Come on!
来吧
Come on.
快点，进去！
Come on! Get in! Come on!
快点！
Come on!
好了，走吧
Okay, now go!
- 快走！ - 不，又再发生了
- Go on! - No, it's happening again!
别让他们把你带走
Don't let them take you away.
我叫你走！
I said, go! Get out of here!
他在哪里？
Where is he?
去死吧
Go to hell.
带她去总部
Take her to headquarters.
我的手下不会在你身上留下痕迹
I promise my men won't leave a mark on you.
长官，我们的朋友康斯又怎样？
Sir. What about our friend Coontz?
若我们让他活着就要付钱给他
If we'd let him live, we'd have to have paid him.
我是说会损失数十万元
We're talking about hundreds of thousands of dollars in damage.
- 摩菲对财物不留情的 - 很好
- Murphy can be rough on properties. - Yeah. Well...
每分每毫的损失 都由你的薪水中扣除
...every cent of it will be coming out of your salaries.
是你们制造他的
Hey! You built him!
我们要进占卡迪拉克区
We're taking Cadillac Heights.
我要你50个手下 一小时后全副武装候命
I'll need 50 of your men armed and in full body armor in one hour. Johnson...
告诉总裁 拆卸人员明早六点可以进入
...tell the CEo the demolition crews will have access at 0600 hours tomorrow.
我们不做那类工作
Hey, we don't do that kind of work.
这是个直接命令
That was a direct order, sergeant.
把市民逐出家园 不是警察的工作
Driving people out of their homes is no work for a cop!
警官
Now, sergeant.
在警队工作15年是一项投资
Fifteen years on the force is quite an investment.
你的工作、你的退休金
Your job, your pension.
别担心那些擅闯者了 想想你的家人吧
Maybe instead of worrying about these squatters, think about your own family.
我有想
I am.
我正在想我要回家面对他们
I'm thinking I have to go home and face them.
你们不能这样做
You can't do this.
你们是OCP的雇员
You are employees of oCP!
记着
Now remember that.
你们在危害自己的退休福利
You're jeopardizing your retirement benefits!
截住那个人
Stop that man.
你和你的朋友们可想赚点钱？
How would you and your friends like to make some money?
- 这是… - 强尼…
- It's... - Johnny...
- 建改队 - 好
- Rehab! - Hurray!
强尼建改队人像 配件和服饰个别发售
Johnny Rehab action figures, parts and accessories all sold separately.
在被认为是机械警察的 最新暴行中…
Three nuns and five clergy are dead...
有三名修女和五名神职人员丧生
...in what is believed to be the latest atrocity by the killer cyborg, Robocop.
OCP宣称该名前度警员…
The OCP claim the former police unit...
在底特律市旧城的卡迪拉克区…
...is responsible for a spree of terrorism...
引发一轮恐怖活动
...in the Cadillac Heights section of Old Detroit.
抱歉，我不能读这个
I'm sorry, I can't even read this.
简直胡说八道，你相信它吗？
This is bullshit! Are you buying this?
你开玩笑嘛 机械战警
Are you kidding me? Robocop?
（临时故障）
玛莉
Marie.
混帐！
Lousy sons of bitches!
- 神经病混蛋 - 没有人会听的
- OCP bastards! - Nobody is listening to you, sweetheart.
我们各就各位
We are in position.
这是大棍，准备就绪 带齐武器进入攻击区
This is Big Stick. You have a green. Arm and proceed to strike zone.
所有队伍，准备就绪
All teams, we have a green.
放松点
Hey, take it easy.
- 现在怎么办？ - 怎么办？
- So what now? - What now?
- 完蛋了，闭嘴吧 - 贝黛的计划又如何？
- Game's over, Moreno. Just shut up. - What about Bertha's plan?
该死，贝黛已经死了
Damn it! Bertha's dead!
对不起
I'm sorry.
各位，大约45分钟后…
Folks, in about 45 minutes...
建改队就会来对付你们
...the Rehabs are coming to blow you out of your neighborhood.
带你们的孩子…
I want you to take your kids...
和任何不能作战的人到地下室
...and anybody who shouldn't be fighting to the basement!
其余的人就受底特律警察部委派
The rest of you are hereby deputized by the Detroit Police Department.
是时候给他们看看警察的厉害
It's time to show how real cops kick ass.
底特律警察，出示你的身分
Detroit Police! Identify yourself.
你因为袭警被拘捕了
You are under arrest for assaulting an officer.
还有破坏警方财物
And destruction of police property.
（动力能量低，需要下载能量）
肃静
Quiet!
别开火，直到有绝对需要
Hold your fire until absolutely necessary.
指挥官…
Commander...
长官，底特律警方在外面 他们在反抗我们
...Detroit Police are out there, sir. They're fighting against us.
那又如何？我们要依期行事的
So? We have a schedule to keep.
我们不可向警察开火 你太过分了
We don't fire on police officers! You're out of line, McDaggett.
我是指挥，由我做主
I'm in charge here. I'm pulling the plug.
坐下
Sit down.
你打仗打疯了？
Have you gone war-wacky?
我叫你坐下
I said, sit down.
好主意
Good idea.
我们怎样离开这里？
How are we getting out of here anyway?
你怎样…算了吧
How'd you get...? Never mind.
外面有没有传讯碟形天线？
Is there a transmission dish outside?
有，我还看到新闻追击 那个傢伙挖鼻孔呢
Yeah, and I was just watching the Media Break guy pick his nose.
你有电脑吗？
Do you have your computer with you?
底特律的市民…
People of Detroit...
这是非法广播，它随时会被截断
...this is an illegal broadcast. It may be cut off at any time.
所以听我说
So listen to me.
OCP在欺骗你们
OCP is lying to you.
他们为了大生意而杀害生命
They're destroying people's lives for big business.
在电视上的那些建改队…
Those Rehabs you see on TV...
他们是OCP聘用的雇佣兵 要把市民逐出家园
...they're mercenaries hired by OCP to throw people out of their homes.
你们要相信我
You've got to believe me.
我代表本市所有无家可归者 失业者…
I'm speaking for all the homeless and jobless citizens of this city...
和每个受资产主义混蛋 管治的城市发言
...and every city like it run by heartless capitalist scumbags...
OCP不关心市民
OCP doesn't care about people. OCP cares about...
反抗吧，否则你的邻居就是下一个
Your neighborhood is next unless you fight back now.
没时间了 OCP就是敌人
Time's running out. OCP's the enemy.
时间不多了  OCP就是敌人
I repeat. Time is running out. OCP is the enemy.
无辜市民正在死去
Help us. Innocent people are dying.
- 给我子弹 - 给我子弹
- More ammo! - More ammo!
泽克中枪了
Zack's hit!
他们会赢，是不是？
They're winning, aren't they, sergeant?
那是什么？
What in the name...?
（瞄准中，聪明炸弹已接合）
长官？
Sir?
来吧，你们这班混蛋
Splatter that, you sons of bitches!
大棍，请通话
Come in, Big Stick.
好吧，机械警察先生
All right, Mr. Robocop.
来抓我吧
Come and get me.
别靠近那扇门
Get away from the door.
考虑一下
Think it over.
我的天，股价跌至零了
Oh, my God, Johnson, our stock has dropped to nothing.
我们完蛋了
We're ruined.
警员，有什么可以效劳？
How may I help you, officer?
拒捕
By resisting arrest.
休想
Don't count on it, chum.
控罪是什么？
Anyway, what's the charge?
谋杀安妮路易斯
The murder of Anne Lewis.
不管死活，你也要束手就擒
Dead or alive, you're coming with me.
你可以要了OCP 它是你的了，再见
McDaggett, you can have OCP. It's all yours. Sayonara.
你去哪里？
Where're you going?
你会错过好戏的
You're gonna miss all the fun.
别逞强了
No flashy bravery, tin man.
否则那两个可人儿会说再见
Or the two cuties say, "Bye-bye."
你干什么？
What are you doing?
制止他们
Stop them! Stop them!
蠢才
Stupid fools!
你可知道你做了什么？！
Don't you know what you've done to us?!
那些机械人装有 热能故障安全设备
Those androids are programmed with a thermal fail-safe device.
你是指自动毁灭？
You mean to self-destruct?
在15秒内 所有二十码内的东西…
In 15 seconds, everything within 20 yards...
都会粉碎
...of where we're standing will be atomized.
你们死定了，笨蛋
We're dead, you stupid slag.
休想
Don't count on it, chum.
坚持住
Hang on.
- 算了 - 让我帮你
- Come on. - Let me give you a hand.
金光先生
Kanemitsu-san...
我明白情况很糟糕
...I realize that it looks bad...
可能我们的计划野心过大
...but maybe our plans were over-ambitious.
我们再合作较小规模的吧
Let's start a skoshy bit smaller.
让我们美化这地区 兴建商场…
Let's gentrify this neighborhood. Build strip malls.
快餐连锁店，大量娱乐设施 你认为怎样？
Fast-food chains. Lots of popular entertainment. What do you think?
- 他说什么？ - 你被开除了
- What did he say? - You're fired.
我得谢谢你
I got to hand it to you.
他们叫你做什么？
What do they call you?
摩菲，是不是？
Murphy, is it?
我的朋友们叫我摩菲
My friends call me Murphy.
你就叫我…
You call me...
机械警察
...Robocop.